Rockville Journal World War II Letters
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Willey, Henry F, undated; Berlin, Germany; Copies by Ruth VonEuw; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willey, Henry F, undated; Berlin, Germany; Copies by Ruth VonEuw; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willey, Henry F, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willey, Henry F, undated; Change of Address,Promotion; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Williams, Robert C, undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Williams, Robert C, undated; Western Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Williams, Robert C, undated; Western Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Williams, Robert C, undated; Oahu; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Williams, Robert C, undated; Hawaii; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Williams, Robert C, undated; Dansville; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Williams, Robert C, undated; Virginia; Seabees; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Edward, undated; Camp Polk; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Francis, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Raymond A, undated; Fort Knox; KY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Clifford, undated; Columbia,SC; Camp Life; Citadel; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Clifford, undated; Fort Benning,GA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Clifford, undated; Fort Bragg,NC; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Clifford, undated; Clemson,SC; City Life; Clemson College; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Raymond A., undated; Cleveland,OH; City Life; High Level Bridge; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Alfred, undated; Fort Harrison, IN; City Life; Indianapolis; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Francis, undated; Orlando, FL; Pine Castle Air Base; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Dorsey, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Francis, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Kenneth, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Dorsey, undated; Atlantic City; NJ; Awaiting Reassignment,Served in Europe; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Dorsey, undated; Army Air Force; Private First Class; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Willis, Francis, undated; Army Air Force; Sargeant; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wilson, Clarence A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wilson, Melvin, undated; Service Update,New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Windus, Edward, undated; APO NYC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Winter, Conrad E, undated; Mrs Frieda Winter; New Address,Wants Newspaper; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wise, Roland, undated; Paris,France; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wisnieski, Stanley J, undated; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wnuk, Valer J, undated; Harlingten; TX; Received Wings; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wnuk, Valer J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wnuk, Valer J, undated; Mrs Ralph Wilcox; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wnuk, Valer J, undated; San Antonio; TX; In Flight Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wnuk, Valer J, undated; 8th Air Force; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wocel, Francis L, undated; Chicago; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wocel, Francis L, undated; Fort Benning; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wocel, Francis L, undated; Camp Stewart; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wocel, Francis L, undated; Fort Benning; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wochomurka, Adolph C, undated; Willington Honor Roll; Killed Luzon,24; Son of Mr and Mrs Charles F Wochomurka; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wochomurka, Adolph C, undated; Battle Description,Medal Posthumously; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wolf, W, undated; Fort H G Wright; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wolf, Owen M, undated; 5th Air Force; Southwest Pacific; Description of Battle; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wolk, Leon C, undated; Chalgrove; Oxfordshire,England; Air Force Welder; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wood, Elizabeth C, undated; Washington; DC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wood, Elizabeth C, undated; Somers Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wood, Ernest, undated; Stafford Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woods, Francis S, undated; France; History of Chemical Warfare Unit; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, Earl, undated; Randolph Field; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, Earl, undated; Randolph Field; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, Earl, undated; Randolph Field; TX; with Photo of Self and Brother; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, Earl, undated; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, Earl, undated; San Antonio,TX; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, George W, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, Earl, undated; Serena Woodward; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, George W, undated; Serena Woodward; Sent Photo to J.I.; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Woodward, George W, undated; San Franciso; CA; Serving at UN Conference in San Francisco; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Worcester, Irene E, undated; Framingham; MA; Reported for Duty at Hospital; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wosel, F, undated; APO; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wowzewicz, J., undated; Richmond,VA; City Life; Hotel John Marshall; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wraight, John E, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wraight, John E, undated; 6th Army; Germany; Info on 57th Signal Battalion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wraight, John E, undated; Miami; FL; Returning Home, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wrona, Francis J, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wrona, Francis J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 1 of 3 Brothers,France; Son of Mrs Stephanie Wrona,6 South Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wrona, Marion J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 1 of 3 Brothers,Holland; Son of Mrs Stephanie Wrona,6 South Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wrona, William J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 1 of 3 Brothers,Burma; Son of Mrs Stephanie Wrona,6 South Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Wytas, Raymond T, undated; 6th Army; France; History of 397th Infantry; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; Letters About Death of John; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; in Combat Filed; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; Filed with Sadlak Papers; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; Fort Benning; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John, undated; Letters from Brother; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John, undated; Seeking Information; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John, undated; Filed with Sadlak Papers; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John, undated; North Africa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John, undated; Letters From Antoni Sadlak About John; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John, undated; Letters From Antoni Sadlak About John; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John, undated; Letters From Antoni Sadlak About John; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; Letters From Antoni Sadlak About John; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; Letters From Antoni Sadlak About John; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; Letters From Antoni Sadlak About John; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed France,31; Son of M&M G Yanishewsky,Wife Sophie; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, John B., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yanishewsky, Terry J, undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yazmer, Solomon, undated; Camp Lucky Strike; near Le Havre; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yazmer, Solomon, undated; Camp Pickett,VA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, Leonard W, undated; Sampson NY; Completed Training; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, Fred, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, Byron P, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed Normandy,28; Son of Mr and Mrs William Yost,96 Grove St; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, Walter, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, William H, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Somers Road; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, Byron P, undated; Bradley Field; CT; Father Will Receive Medal for Son KIA; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, Byron P, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Assigned to Combat Duty; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, William H, undated; Italy; Bomber Group Given Award; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Yost, Byron P, undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagora, Bruno A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Brooklyn Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Joseph L, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Joseph L, undated; Manila; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Joseph L, undated; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Joseph L, undated; Tokyo; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Louis J, undated; Belgium; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Louis J, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Louis J, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Louis J, undated; Fort Devens; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Louis J, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Louis J, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Louis J, undated; Swannanoa; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zagura, Louis J, undated; Fort Devans; MA; Discharge Form,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zahner, Emanuel, undated; Camp Wolters, TX; Camp Life; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zale, Joseph, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zaresky, Alexander, undated; San Diego; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zaresky, Alexander, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zawacki, Theodore J, undated; France; Description of Mobile Ord Depot Unit; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zbyk, Frank J, undated; Camp Gruber; Wins Badge; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zelinka, N, undated; Camp Stoneman; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zepperling, William M, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziebarth, Frank E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed Italy,27; Son of Mrs Edward Burns, Wife Madeline; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziebarth, Frank E., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Ladimer W, undated; Fort Bragg,NC; Camp Life; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Casimir J, undated; Southwest Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Ladimer W, undated; Nashville; TN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Ladimer W, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Ladimer W, undated; Fort Bragg; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Ladimer W, undated; Nashville; TN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Ladimer W, undated; Nashville; TN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Casmir J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Ziemba, Ladimer W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zinsser, Burton, undated; Fort McClellan; AL; Achieved High Marksman Score; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zugura, Louis, undated; Swannanoa, NC; "Old Glory"; See Zagura, Louis J; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zugura, Louis, undated; Humor; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zugura, Louis, undated; Swannanoa, NC; Scenery; Asheville,NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zugura, Louis, undated; Swannanoa, NC; Scenery; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zuraw, Edward, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed Luzon,26; Son of Mr and Mrs Frank Zuraw,South Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)
  - Zuraw, Edward, undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Si-Z)